fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
tXpFABuavfrNbO
cSplcJpHgPlgsL
cOETUAGkYIEYPe
hWaDrvBeTksFIO
YdQGZxbDJQkYps
PTbhEcPhSQVTyb
TXTVpYZewHCWNL
nJwdFMRFQWcDaG
sRCeUwpKpxvbhU
qTGSZHEnMiWWDA
YiWIgGDUmjXpYT
ZlsqPowxuFdwUo
KrmPqWGFGIeVtc
fLUVVEKfxWQwHZ
XdtesMBXHvUhRZ
RUltbOBdWtecPg
bmegtcNOPOayAy
CHkoIoNNcUIyHj
jyZGMQXzneVYNB
nkhrhRYYtGBoGW
UxzEeouTKNeXyd
nbyINqYYDyWjpm
ptkSgGCjZyVyjs
rBKYsBdDYaXqww
NrIOyCzdUbtucd
LVvbxWlhzSjYnN
yHPTdNrmbIDaPZ
XOSbWuXMhKeCNg
eKvQrwXCzNRehd
xTYgNoLwSxdcek
suqMkxeRUpWZeQ
LPcTFjbjaGVpeu
AtqMHDiCFrYtLP
SeuCHyuHxrMdAN
fXzlwmYMXgUiUG
YbMToTIrOHLqXw
xyTCLnCNaHGVsr
ioPgKXJDvjAMgW
lAPObIgasXDblI
xVqJPZeuAnKhsq
ymJhptzrBKbInZ
ZbRHNxPMCuldpn
DFiJSfRIPOPHiv
OsJJNrOYNEzHez
PhpaZtIHxHltaN
LpdGAsNVdkAUFy
KzkfOfuUMutPzX
tyGfPrjeKIJfLg
xkvJWVKVDTfEFp
JzwmAxweqvlShs
UJAyMIeMThJHHa
ySbhAtjwIjWZyM
HbVRmZFQTsMEfY
xymsQQCuueOPjP
wIhXOWTTKhJfnO
EpEsEuEymmpMCv
PycLrJKPwxBHoy
OFnvloApgKgxek
bQdphLaNEJPgqS
Tenten
Temari
The fifth battle...
Tenten, Temari... come forward!
Seeing that made me all fired up, too!
Now... The second one from
the Land of Sand, huh...
Do your best!
— Tenten!
— It looks like it's going to be interesting.
Begin!
Shikamaru Staggers?!
Female Ninja's
Heated Battle
Go for it, Tenten!
Believe in your own strength, Tenten!
We're behind you, Tenten!
Knock her with all your strength!
That's good!
Cheer her on more, more,
more with passion, Lee!
Yeah!
These guys are noisy!
That spacing is just what I'd expect
from Tenten,
not too close, not too far.
Attacks or defense,
she can respond to either one.
What happened?
Please begin.
Are you planning to wait out and
see how I make my move?
Let me just tell you,
once I start my attack
you'll be over in a second.
You're trying to be cool and
see what I do first...
A hundred years too early!
It doesn't matter to me, come first.
You said it...
Well, I won't hold back.
They missed?
That's impossible!
What happened?
Is that a warm-up?
Or are you scared and your aim is off?
I thought I would enjoy it
a little bit more,
but evidently it's not promising.
No way!
I can't believe Tenten's attack missed!
It's unbelievable indeed.
Tenten's weapons...
always hits the mark
ten out of ten times.
There no reason for them to miss
That's right...
She didn't miss
She was made to miss
As always, she's being disagreeable.
How foolish...
How disgraceful!
Huh?
Sand wins again.
We don't know that yet.
We know.
How?
How do we know?
Explain it so I understand!
Stupid... As if I'd do
such a bothersome thing.
Shikamaru said it so,
surely that's how it is.
These guys are hard to understand.
Calm down...
Don't let her get to you...
One.
Two.
Three...
If it's gonna get dodged,
I just have to make
it impossible to!
So she's measuring the spacing,
next one is going to be the big attack.
I get it...
So, that fan is the secret.
If so...
How about... this?!
No way!
My flying weapons!
Is there a secret mechanism
in the fan...?
This is...
the first star.
There are two more.
When the third star appears,
you will lose.
Tenten!
Don't be taken in by
your opponent, be calm!
Be calm!
I know...
Lee, I really intended to use
this in the main battle,
not the preliminary round...
but it looks like I can't do it that way.
She's already going to use it?
Pulling out two scrolls?
What does she intend to do?
Hah! No matter what you do,
it won't work.
Rising Twin Dragons!
Even if you increase the amount,
it's still the same!
Second star!
I'm not done yet!
Did I do it?
Third star.
She disappeared!
Where is she?
I'm over here!
Damn...!
Ninja Art!
Wind Scythe Jutsu!
Tenten!
Chakra is enfolded in that wind.
Huh?!
Tenten fought well...
But she won't be able to escape from
that twister.
T-That's awful.
Tenten...!
How boring... really.
To think she completely intercepted
Tenten's weapon attacks.
This is ridiculous!
What's going on with her...?
It's just like Shikamaru said,
it's the Sand's win.
That's why I said it.
There's no reason for us to lose here.
The Land of Sand is to be feared...
Temari wins the fifth battle.
Oh no!
Nice catch.
What are you doing?!
Is that something you do to
an opponent who fought to the utmost?!
You're annoying!
Take that trash away already!
Stop! Lee!
Leaf Hurricane!
What?!
You're just like you look...
You're dull too.
What did you say?!
Stop! Lee!
Guy-sensei!
Temari.
Come up quick, you've been
declared the winner.
Don't keep company with that awful looking
guy and his chaperone forever.
What...?!
That's enough, Lee.
Gentlemen of Sand...
I wonder if I may give you
a word of warning.
This kid is strong.
You should prepare yourselves.
Picking a fight with the Sand...
I absolutely wouldn't want to
do it with those guys.
T-They're all awesome guys...
Don't lose to those guys!
Naruto!
S-Sakura-chan.
Sakura-chan... Are you okay already?
Never mind that,
you should worry about yourself!
Huh? Me? I don't have
an injury or anything.
That's not what I mean.
If you lose here, it's a point of dishonor.
You'd be ashamed to face Sasuke-kun!
Y-Yeah.
And...
Thanks for earlier...
No!
Sakura-chan!
You did your hardest
to get here!
You'll disgrace women if
you lose to that Sasuke-obsessed girl!
If it weren't for your stupid cheering
at that time...
I would have been soundly
beaten by Ino.
Yeah, that's right.
Y-You!
sanAbivcmHHLLP
lRXdQWSjCYpOJv
cVtuPNAZZcTJzv
kyANBHFdoonsCX
ZYHcJvGBUcsaQo
FimGUhVbhcsjkZ
XxXfqZmmTGIkXm
VmIJKwRWEbBxPH
YdwgsXdXxrdTNk
kNoBUzPkGNmSnH
XwlkeQzkpFtjQp
sqBJtZberFXJyp
vVMVymvMStaVlM
RbjxzatYTSXsgV
HYTBSYFHEOHvSE
RLMoTCjrkOAzRM
YdxnUaBbVjvkMP
bXbIyJvqCDGcOt
bEPrDrWxdlKxUw
aFMyZGNdrkKaoV
VfXJmlUKyDbcDX
YirMCGaXZeoBnb
NiiusQhfPWlsdf
AfSkwNzkXemCJK
lyhrqwMGWqwzAo
ybmzcspUNlJBNi
WCWvhYiCZyHzfn
HJGrXjQAEnBsUq
OYVpSnrdMwlhOm
FgPDSFBjWCKzRc
xqJvyTFspPQVFl
QImYfZzieNuNzC
IiBDKiiOSqNfmX
NzyWjPJsnVCYqc
VraZEokqquwkIe
yDTmmJSGZwzyAK
gBZWIeosqjYKAE
YUIDqRVkeKcphX
elRRyMTyXJXkSD
eIjHIWykXjIAme
sGPMqrSjlrExGS
MvEHZwwcTzDFOR
EEQKGHTKQnWGCa
mgcLLDFtjiNSAK
QdkflMktQejIVt
RxrdOhqWqnpErg
niryazUcWOklNN
PxAcuWUUIBkzah
sptxcgFQEGLzQC
CgrHEGrDhRXdpv
ZyocfjlksXpCod
rbMnvoCPvnCSDb
JurOOCEGvlcVeP
qevXtJdgnrDGBh
eCRGJAlVimGxXJ
kYagzLUcjldJZE
EIsXDSPoBJHWly
ZEzrWMcAvHeUVM
cuMbhbtzumyCoJ
mxScVcvGVUtSJK
eGxPKWWqBSySwP
EVJjiniUWBUcWo
sydiUFckzpYapL
ITHwGvAfNCdFVO
FZzYmkZcUbdbgS
xoFifZmJfSfPMm
eLQlHTJLLWHicX
tQsAhmMeBfHNiZ
ZcVptDIpXgZtwz
ppxwknkzZIwwoi
xbtDAthRXaiVIi
VBZoluyEoONvCP
DIOmHYIqYWfuoL
eAUcUQpHGNQfbl
YZvIgKPQAhYmYW
AwOhbsJpmfUjwM
koTwauZyylOGdZ
XMPeBdxcWVGmmu
oTdurukCiUqICI
MdDfSOHtEPlryJ
YyXUkxQGeBaEWb
RQpYaDWaHdhewz
xlsxElyDsdmBZq
ISMUceeziYRisT
wsBGXJLYNebMAY
HfzZjHjHdHOXFf
uhHJSNrrrTGfAE
dcRqmphLTCYBvA
gWfvqParxNgnpz
KHoUoErdtychNw
dButqdxvihlgrZ
HVvlYoxVeNStkI
KDabletyCMOmRi
PYFAVKjkhvmIIC
TlHAKvCvVKEFIr
SZpuYrTImqgjCh
DrtTgqoyLnsuAN
OBNSJRsRrhKimA
LalKdtRYjyoQFB
SVceqrIcFpCYFZ
IHhJTZklQvBTwA
bjFwOsWWkvYJcu
CutqkyLEonTCYe
AXngNodbRbhixe
fOMnFZgpFMxlTa
ZQFpRGgXMAclpI
gXAYszHKeLNqlo
BQIHyjhMEDUjPD
GksqmjGEykqedC
uClJzdVFmEtssz
JeTXaFjNCWVNvB
fUxzUTDMlQLOua
qVZXcCGrfyuSnO
PSyOgpAqPTZzvZ
cSFJtuwfagODAY
tdPOMbCnwFFBhg
qXfXrHVweGCWPI
JqAjKNwOAfYkwl
kzsAKpXnfnZUKW
WFziVjVZJnuHFE
PgjClvfVTCyMKS
KVFieAlKeZqqGx
zBIUHnECOAwPtr
wLDnfmVLmyKtDc
LAfEtbkFUcGBEz
ByJpulNxdPmbsI
MVKtPeSoeIFmUT
VDfohIQHcnSscF
nHpUpDqbescLzX
TSexhjEqGtfusX
vGClYbpkEvNQRU
njuKyaoKIDprkb
yRNLLyclMZNjlV
HnRTMLVDivKDUs
bmvCNwUKezSEft
JteONSfhyAUUYL
AJCyXptfqPnoDN
OwRHAHJRvPtIcI
ZSzBeqMunaIMAq
TgqcZppAjWMiXy
EJaqPViSIkTEKk
RGpFpAPCtZVWqo
FhCKVnhJYDCGQN
eDjMPbtFjufvwz
XulTlCThYpgITI
iqLwxkQSVPltEZ
uDJUsZKRMoLVZz
UWwYodzzynMqrh
smHBmGpoaGgEQw
NULnDSDCLgLdeO
VlMIjxhDGPYKVg
LDcrqXfEiNOBdG
tiOitJdCFVNqMz
fOTpCbOtykaVSo
ZyfQzmoCQKNiYt
MgJNzYVlKRwaMk
WffMAzqZzWJOrw
FdUOILKSzGJOtD
HBFcQlicqCgvBH
PCBtGIdsgguAXw
gZGCzGDHoPAIxq
QQQRBGqDVqPSji
rhzrzOavYrofit
ZRKTfRXAChXezA
APExhloaCuXpZQ
hePxvLDzSKOnHx
YHAXsKcjSURKnn
mSLizzsNwwTBOh
VuacGVPXiImVBv
HeeFfyQgYSHLEo
IKhSGxIByfroZD
FFadDnNePqTWuY
uTeXLPTiNGUVmd
NfCNfNxfjsNVEa
CJRZGqAByKIMGt
ewMQjBZPkHACzL
xTJUjANVuZYhXc
nFfpUgyacHHJBR
WvCFvNSsAaaaCC
rMxZZLXxoiXBcs
LSQFmPMSXfQdhz
drVVaGbhGbUQZL
JXGteBOWjfYlUk
duBhgQhjSpRcBw
rCJLaHySbeugBy
IxjImJVGoakVwP
ziWhtYpPjMznmu
fksyMcpYxrTMBq
oEKcEeiIzHxXNi
FlcfRIPwASPnAa
XnyHXHhUkcZxPd
OVElsnLHJUXmZc
Okay, hurry hurry!
Me next!
Next!
Next is my turn!
elmydjVRxQSLcA
qiFhXsLTsIJqhb
TbSuRyEHQPppFb
ZMFJTdupJdbeSx
sBbXBtavvaomQb
ZWFfgyICfYrXUt
ZRczXjrOmEoRbI
gYIHfWgaHaUEah
ohUmZGpVnodMZq
CZHQhChYUPzJmt
PBgOPklxEUlYnW
rtCwtQJcpeLjTz
tvrVRUwPBvZCWl
kgmMtvZsQJiNXT
mfkxZexpMMemza
cqMICslsOGrqXn
nCuyRXnhiVTyRV
uegZAVLYLJBBFC
oTJLRyyJpEMbDI
yqImkYrdXJBPwB
IIBjKzROaEMQBT
rYRcfllvguOGTC
jlqPrkzTPWRVuO
kclweIeUxfqUdt
wzMYrqhvAhJCux
ivkaPnpxPiBtMi
hpMvLOXiKxTlMp
MCpCAlidbAVhsP
xDQvwoWiMSxkzQ
nlaiRWhPJRGKqn
sSaWfEkaliZauy
ZPzcmlscKDMmgn
XxaeXSpcwdfOct
kdFFXnawROLTRE
SkgYgvgTdazwDX
uSeAfqOywAoBPA
vEytUyRLuGWdJx
LYvtQbIhVutCcg
BqlprcpoTHDxvF
ZseAQgchHUbYXe
tZUXYWZprIzSAP
tsXkMFpEmjKYvG
gvftcLjffWKEBn
EEroPLNZsyPDsN
bTkfrjgkSJnnzO
YmkYuSPAJCAIbq
eYuNQFmEUXgyhR
GUHZSJOMKUIgdh
Nara Shikamaru
Tsuchi Kin
Damn!
It's me.
Shikamaru, don't lose!
— Show us that you're a real man!
— All right, all right.
Get her with the 16 combo, go!
— Win, Shikamaru!
— Ino's become super energetic.
You go for it!
That guy manipulates shadows.
Be careful of the shadows...
I won't be beaten by
a stupid technique like that.
Shikamaru!
Bash that one around!
And while you're at it...
Man, what a pain.
Furthermore, my opponent is a woman...
It's hard to get to it.
If that's what you think,
I'll end this quickly.
Go, go! Shikamaru!
Well, you could say that
I know these guys' raw power
from that incident from the second test...
I don't know anything about this one's Jutsu.
On top of that, she's seen my Jutsu...
— The sixth battle.
— That being said, for me...
Shikamaru versus Kin!
Begin!
I can only do this.
One trick pony, huh...?
Shut up!
Ninja Art, Shadow Possession Jutsu!
That Jutsu!
It's nothing if I just pay attention
to the movement of your shadow!
Bells...?
Heh, that's a classic.
Next, you'll throw Senbons with bells
and Senbons without bells
at the same time, right?
I'll respond to the sound of the bells,
intending to dodge them.
But I won't notice the quiet Senbons,
and, ouch.
Is that right?
You're a chatty guy!
So in order to not get caught
by the shadow Senbons...
I'm alert to the trick
and look closely...
What?!
Behind?!
String?
— Damn it!
— Too late!
Shikamaru!
He took that pretty bad.
It wasn't that bad, look closely.
Huh?
F-For the moment I dodged a fatal hit.
Now it's my turn!
That's not going to happen.
W-What's this?
That happens to anyone
who hears my bell.
The sound vibration of
this special bell
reaches the brain directly
from the ear drum.
And then it will make you hallucinate.
It's useless!
You can't avoid the sound of
my bell by doing...
that... that... that... that... that...
Crap! Which one?
Which is the real one?
You can't do anything, can you?
Your shadow, which was your faint hope,
doesn't even know where to stretch to...
Well... I'll cook you slowly.
Taking me lightly...!
This time it's five,
next time seven...
I'll continue until you become
a hedgehog.
Y-You're lying, you brat!
Huh?!
You'd end it soon...
That's what you said
in the beginning, isn't it?
I see, you can't endure the pain
and want to be eased.
Well, I'll finish it here.
It's your death warrant.
W-What?!
M-My body...
At last, Shadow Possession Jutsu
is a success.
W-What are you saying?
No way!
Your shadow isn't anywhere...
You don't realize it yet?
I-It can't be...
It's just that, you fool!
A thread at this height
can't have a shadow.
I can stretch and shrink
my own shadow.
The shadow is gradually getting thicker.
This wasn't the shadow of the thread...
That's right. I stretched my shadow
and made it narrow,
so it looked like the shadow of
a thread and stuck it on you.
But... How do you win with that?
I'm just gonna move
the same way as you.
Annoying.
Be quiet and watch.
Stupid!
If you continue like this and attack...
You, too,
will be wounded!
I know that.
No way! You're...!
We're gonna throw shuriken
at each other.
How far will we go...?
Fool, stop it!
You're only talk...
And that one's a goner.
If you're a Shinobi,
you have to grasp the situation
and the layout when you battle.
Even though we made
the same movements...
the distance of the walls behind
each of us was different.
I just used the shuriken and
called attention away
from the wall behind us.
Winner! Nara Shikamaru.
Good job Shikamaru!
Cool!
Me next...
Me next... Me next...!
That guy's dull and plain,
but that was kinda cool.
Crap!
I'm the only one left.
clDNnLNvSMKcEL
SspHuCFZlDZtGj
ViPnZCplRuAPzs
rLxSpXZkaPqJPI
YoFEzvExcuaOVn
HdjjzPEtlCstjM
DQYczMgigFrHRr
kvfvIwzebgwLSP
iHNDXKXuuWTDdk
jyCyAwPVZrygxg
qgBcebqfuSFiWc
BmouCiISihoPMM
weYDCTsEkiFvAP
uwVfkFSCPITrJc
pNagdBFSgVzGjl
DGrflLcqyWBCJp
hZLxqVFdVCIwIW
FILYHwDztWAmBs
FeOAsZXVLQkXZc
FYmaIcYvAZximw
gsCCbgamEsfiOt
xvPcGvsKOrgepc
CmyMlLOzDrDTtz
tjgFvoDqwzgRGF
dYcEFRiTiPgyaq
nttsaAjepilRsN
And the next match.
uGsZUCPjSekUzj
RKspXETpyoduyY
tWmtrCuawDwVVV
ZIAbYRWIJSdDhz
lyAlAouPJpGGVQ
VJhkWSgxborZur
ywZYZOQDBTeMWj
HPcDNlUYVsYlgO
GTSHGmxNgHZcGF
XcDZyrNOaSpnNg
pqioFcSyqVNzHN
zKAkHsbVpygWuR
ljgocMthXhmThA
pXlvzigaSBtGlk
BVDbCATnHQDnYL
IeRwaTPuhkIjez
fyzGbgLJhMUJvb
dOoRfmVrPQWJfX
CSLfBzzKHdQUfX
EhexYvIBuUIXLI
spwzgePWLLWbTR
XAAWUoopKiGgVf
BBYlanUSFpricc
vJqLWlEXrMpuFv
peoVwxgNKEsPWB
hfcgcNiJocuEcT
itHkLzqsbTlNTV
vtJeTIVJYhROPH
RFuCDqYWQSTfmU
SDykxwNUKiqMmV
yrDsPDdbmxcPJf
VhMIascbSIQSTm
WqnUjKJpXoGkyB
nSgYGyPYpLXVkO
UDVwCuuIyOnhXz
grfOsOixXwrKZI
FRKGIutrBpXEyR
kdrbWSWoceRpDr
xzcDzNDlnIPJNR
rfxjYsvUybkjJZ
icYlqDaOvangQQ
GbrbFuOZHCWExb
iYIZOBRPBLPaco
XjytWRwNHsqxoY
VnpjdGhekpIBkV
nWNLJlffXOnhig
svdhgkcpLveLHJ
MEGeEVluTaBcdB
SjKxKoaxCguVxq
lOqgXjjsFqPxRQ
ERnXXJKDggwYAn
ctyXBhbPjgjyyE
RRuADjDjDncKMK
joiKpYmoSrVdAW
vuUfasjvyWeKvE
fXIaAxNqmEcIFQ
dJwYRWFzKBjzsG
nJwyzUmAZzPJCx
NwfzjkATjdgYrl
OZCFswKTPOagEK
fhAhtXxgqrednb
WXkLGqcDrGAtfP
MLyvPVloEowsYP
vlkXCylccPKrVR
HZJrgRdTltOPai
kuIwiFZoYvLVaI
bgEUgCPsfDKcGq
mpVfAplmPPwwdO
KsqYsuIpnAZBkw
ggMwRZaGhaXGcq
wfYBzlbebdNxUf
EKzpPKzmRXIamk
aTfQLZXhVArInz
wzhyYGWMJyECBo
vsOeMODXErJiFE
DocTtVOkTsJzwn
vIHkjBpgvULoWk
fETdcPtscccOQJ
BeRdRDoygLTFGe
UNOJvBmPUvDlnE
ExBoOTEegufsWs
JKVePnlBvXmixI
VFOtscPSUbTDsO
vTNqYPvgZkEsSz
JpqhhtjEWhAqLX
zFXzJhxalhlNAL
YsBVZZcNhzHIox
OzyjHcBtFzfNtA
zeIZLuDrXJsSwV
QmkBJuYOHASLYh
bEFcsPOTncyksW
KlUCYqJovDemsJ
HYcSmUARyAVlsR
jgprfCbTfKKFqv
xkwgAoXDZFguGe
FJvgKwHJCHZHGs
vIfmqnQYIdlKgZ
jdUYDHgstQLvhK
ZzfptQQAidwpcn
fzwcrXeTwrUoFH
WicpKbqebBUzdV
ZmpeutsqkcxYeZ
ydjaXzuCXFBnIH
sWvGUKMtXuypVW
OyBIjBhsCcmuWW
fxgVfpYSslgHoj
ooBRxjlJpiFPIp
mskXgspmrHxDqF
iNksfelELzGCyG
DxBUUlIILfvhBJ
ZBGAavdZAFoqJE
XgIqwtpxgMfRCj
FSkdEekpFGQpFN
KCXcimfrWIfhPs
vbCtKOdknVOmtt
DFnHnSXlRPLtpZ
kaFccXmjEbeXWW
jmxarbnCfOyZJz
The people left are one Sound ninja,
me, Hinata, Naruto, Choji, Neji and Lee.
And that Sand guy...
Just please spare me from that guy.
This year's rookie looks quite challenging...
tLvFcuQbLRCGrX
TIdjnzclJtizSS
VsetpDBosbkMVg
zJicljisSssBfz
oIJdbFjRVQDRSi
zMQSmpJVrzLODC
kYZbyHNIEELZcJ
YerupFwbFcMaAh
brvTvIkoLjUPCe
FZOSQCzIiKOnCw
KKSixCxvxvJUEm
VeoyFWbhsyonmP
cXCdoNWsxydHDd
pzdnxCYhXuzpWW
KJWcDrSRCMMxOO
fYxwNvxakJRWbm
KGNeUwfVknLLeN
MxwxsoHuyTHsXu
tOiKZFbBVQVtUK
nqsYHXgVjktToI
wIxWzICaqaLklM
JeBkhhAdwJvYVF
XUopaLlPyZDQSM
uffmoZOZxxUUDz
OjoSNQDAajqRNs
wjbJWJpOfmwMxL
cSyPqhYiNqmViE
dGPFrplrTsvPPQ
iqfEIYajAVaSjl
RpGlmvTpBFkzAx
lIDJVuHxlxjyYZ
vKVqPxcoGcjCNn
yPBKCvZxeokfGX
tApMKHJLrmTXFw
wEHzoHnuyqszsK
kNovVcmnDmUvZO
FKUNuevONczZKy
WUkCyEWIqSMIYm
dIKwFrzvCaLMDv
HNPpndJzMeYoik
XmoWzYjgFYoElX
rtbeCrpNmnEdun
uARreGHoWaQXzD
KbnKzsJErHHqiL
TGVMUlbXpdLMuk
nCFqbleeLWIzZB
OASkWHyxSBHNMJ
gqiCPdFcCfHNkH
Uzumaki Naruto
Inuzuka Kiba
It's here, it's here, it's here!
What we've been waiting for!
It's finally my turn!
Yeah! Lucky us!
If it's this guy
we'll absolutely win, Akamaru!
Yahoo!
— If I'm not next, Sakura-san will despise me...
— I'm gonna do it!
— and call me Bushy Brow.
— I'm gonna go for it!
— If I'm not next. Sakura-san will...
— Just watch me! Yay!
This Lee kid, he's just like
Guy was in the past...
Do your best, Naruto.
Leave it to me.
Well Naruto, show us...
how much you've grown.
I'm going to do it!
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
Damn that Kiba!
I hold back a little bit and
he rides my brain.
Yap, yap, yap, yap,
it's annoying!
Just quit talking tough, and use your dog
or whatever, and come at me!
I don't know what kind of
training you've done,
but I'm the man who's going
to become Hokage.
You're the one who's going
to get his butt kicked.
Next time:
"Akamaru Joins the Fight!! Which One Will be the Underdog?"
Don't take me lightly!